<sentence> 0
A sports article in some copies on Sunday about <LOCATION>Boston</LOCATION> 's 1-0 victory against <LOCATION>San Francisco</LOCATION> referred incorrectly to the history of the interleague series between the <ORGANIZATION>Red Sox</ORGANIZATION> and the <ORGANIZATION>Giants</ORGANIZATION> .
</sentence>

<sentence> 1
This was their first meeting since June 2004 -- not since the World Series in 1912 , the year they last played each other at <LOCATION>Fenway Park</LOCATION> .
</sentence>